== sync, corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
(Sheldon(on phone):)Hello, yes, I was hoping
you could help me.
(Sheldon(on phone):)What song is this?
♪ La, la, la, la, la, la, la. ♪
(Sheldon(on phone):)You don't know?
(Sheldon(on phone):)Well, how dare you
call yourselves
(Sheldon(on phone):)a Rock and Roll Hall of Fame?
(Sheldon(on phone):)My goodness. Do you sing along
to the greatest hits
(Sheldon(on phone):)of Elvis Presley
with that mouth?
(Sheldon(on phone):)Well, they were no help at all.
Which is crazy,
(Leonard:)since rock and roll is all
about good customer service.
(Penny:)Yeah. So you have a song
stuck in your head.
(Penny:)It happens to everybody.
(Sheldon:)Well, I'm not everybody.
I have an eidetic memory.
(Sheldon:)I should be able to remember
what song this is,
(Sheldon:)but I can't.
(Sheldon:)Something's wrong with me.
(Penny:)I told you if we were patient,
he'd figure it out for himself.
Oh... I was always afraid
this day would come.
(Sheldon:)This might be the first step
of my descent into madness,
(Sheldon:)where I gradually test
the limits of public nudity.
(Penny:)Public nudity?
(Leonard:)Eh, that just means
going barefoot.